one-bearing stocks to watch. So, traditionally, I'm covering the research from the capacity perspective from the interviews
available in the Josh Stage list. I'm already
covering it a
little bit in the last named quarter. So,
if the revenue from injectables in the last 12 months is the
highest
here and is visible.
According to the doctor's name, I'll tell you first, what is
its growth here,
they have reduced it by 10.35%. If I
look at round four, 3000 crore kabaddi,
this trick is done by
Gland Mama. Students will
try to explain youth. The
name of our stock is Gland Farm Socho.
If you look at it, it definitely means a lot of
positive for the company. This company
is such a friend or in million dollar terms, we are
trying to do it from Gland Mama. The
research team finally brought it with them as well. The
video ends here. Let's
talk about the 400 million dollar stock,
just from the promoters are Chinese.  So,
I have talked about the pipeline of certain products. There is no blind faith in it, that
only organic rose, that is, those who
came for work, to understand its
revenue and the best part about this is that by being a little
watchful, someone is
talking about expanding their own business,
going to analyze and discuss the same, in the sense that
Gland Pharma is already getting back to
revenue, that by selling these products, one in
organic rose, that is,
we should not have any new questions, so
what about that stock, we have watched
Indore Injectables product, which
is the first reason here because the
company is ready to do stock watch, more than that should be done, so
you start the video from here
where their maximum stand is that,
I hope that this short video is about the
pipeline of certain products,
which is from injectables to 11 injectables,
you must have liked it, if you people think, then
I have told the names, it is
line and specifically in injectables.  The
company has reserves of ₹5000, a
good thing even the existing ones, they
have the injectable of USFDA,
that I am doing good work, so
first of all like and target will be 500, this
investment and when you visit the end
product from the injectable, there
is also this DJ this triangle of
question companies, this company has
our model, do not subscribe to the police, it is
in the shortage list, that is the
end of the video, we are
seeing good volume growth of 1 lakh on Twitter, so it is
available, so do not forget about acquisitions there also,
friends, you guys can use the promo,
more availability of this flower is now foreign
- so it has been achieved, next you
can use Twitter and for fifty five percent the
company is looking forward to and the
visibility is of Arvind or
of a particular product and that product,
then the growth of both of those diseases, as
I told you, compliance point of
Wahgaon, we are giving you people fennel
Festival discount that you can get from our website
can produce it does Gila me
cent voting when will I get it so next
visibility because here plan for me
view is very consistent this company
twitter this promo code if you use it you
get it whether it is Hind
Informa so here which means normally when you
see their
small cardamom in the market from the audit of all the days some of the
highest ever discount of 5 per cent and if there are any
such products then definitely find a key so
that kind of access
presents a dice also provide market
present please you will get only 45 it has something
from USFDA so if you do
n't see Akhilesh company being seen then
you can subscribe to it so
and specifically develop the market if we
are developing injectables which are
soft corner definitely those producers
why to watch the platform is
addressed here blend mama
present in the US FDA shortage list it remains so that
we among
Today we will understand about the note, in many
ways
this is the biggest advantage for the company,
which means visibility of test results,
reject two, if you look at the compliance issues, there is a crack, something is like this in
Indian,
that too is quite strong, now like we
or if you look at the consistency, then it is very,
if there is a Chinese company because the promoter
told that the injectables which are shot fast are very
good, grant for them, thanks for the
Chineseairplanemode,sentstake on the wicket
[Music]